Guide to the Jean O'Barr Papers, 1974-2011 RL.00968
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Jean O'Barr papers
1974-2011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
O'Barr, Jean F.
RL.00968
18.6 Linear Feet
Professor and founder of Duke University's Women's Studies program. Materials from the founding and operation of Duke's Women's Studies program, including proposals, reviews, and annual reports. Also includes scrapbooks with photographs and conference materials; correspondence about the Women's Studies program; and publications about O'Barr and the Women's Studies program. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
13,950 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research, with the exception of boxes 13 and 15, which are closed to research until 2036 and 2065, respectively.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Jean O'Barr Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2010.
Biographical Note
Jean Fox O'Barr was a professor and founder of Duke University's Women's Studies program, as well as a co-founder of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Chronology List
1964 B.A., Indiana University
1965 M.A., Northwestern University
1969 Joined the faculty at Duke University
1970 Ph.D., Northwestern University
1971-1983 Dean, Continuing Education, Duke University
1976 Editor, Language and Politics (The Hague: Mouton)
1976 Author, Third World Women: Factors in Their Changing Status (Durham: Duke University Comparative Area Studies Program)
1983 Founded the Women's Studies Program, Duke University
1984 Editor, Signs: Journal of Women in Culture and Society (journal)
1987 Women's Studies graduate courses began, Duke University
1987 Editor (with Sandra Harding), Sex and Scientific Inquiry (Chicago: University of Chicago)
1988 Co-founded the Women's Studies Archivist position (later became the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture), Duke University
1989 Editor, Women and a New Academy: Gender and Cultural Contexts (Madison, WI: University of Wisconsin)
1992 Editor (with Mary Wyer), Engaging Feminism: Students Speak Up and Speak Out (Charlottesville, Va.: University of Virginia)
1992 Jean O'Barr Fund established by Duke University alumnae
1994 Undergraduate major established in Women's Studies, Duke University
1994 Author, Feminism in Action: Building Institutions and Community through Women's Studies (Chapel Hill, NC: University of North Carolina)
1998-2001 Named the first Margaret Taylor Smith Director of Women's Studies, Duke University
2000 University Distinguished Service Professor, Duke University (The first woman in Duke's history to be so named)
2000 Jean Fox O'Barr Professorship of Women's Studies chair awarded to Duke University by Lee/Ewing Foundation
2008 Retired, Duke University
Collection Overview
The collection consists largely of O'Barr's files and materials from the founding and operation of Duke University's Women's Studies Department. It includes proposals, reviews, and annual reports. Also includes scrapbooks with photographs and conference materials; correspondence about the Women's Studies program; and publications about O'Barr and the Women's Studies program. Also includes reviews of other women's studies programs throughout the United States; pamphlets and projects relating to the Women's Studies Department; materials relating to the founding of SIGNS magazine; student papers discussing gender; published and unpublished articles by O'Barr, including surveys of women at Duke, writings by O'Barr related to her African studies, and articles about women in academia and the workplace; graduate studies by O'Barr relating to Africa and anthropology; book reviews; and other miscellaneous material. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Women's studies -- Universities and colleges -- United States; Feminism and higher education; Women's studies -- Education, Higher -- United States; Scrapbooks; Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture; Duke University. Women's Studies Department; Duke University; O'Barr, Jean F.
- Accession (2010-0200), 1974-2010, 4 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Accession (2010-0200) (6.0 lin. ft.; 4500 items; dated 1974-2008) includes materials from the founding and operation of Duke's Women's Studies program, including proposals, reviews, and annual reports. Also includes scrapbooks with photographs and conference materials; correspondence about the Women's Studies program; and publications about O'Barr and the Women's Studies program.
  - Establishing Women's Studies Major
    - Proposal for Women's Studies Major, 1992-1996 (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Women's Studies Review, 10-11 April 1997 (4 folders) (Box 1)
    - Women's Studies Program Review, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - Women's Studies Annual Reports
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1983-1986 (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1986-1987 and 1987-1988 (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1988-1989 (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report Copy 2, 1988-1989 (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1989-1990 (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1990-1991 (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1990-1991 (3 of 3 folders) (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1991-1992 (3 folders) (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1992-1993 (4 folders) (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1993-1994 (3 folders) (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1994-1995 (4 folders) (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1995-1996 (5 folders) (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1996-1997 (1 of 4 folders) (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1996-1997 (2-4 of 4 folders) (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1997-1998 (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Program Annual Report, 1998-1999 (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - Scrapbooks, Correspondence, Photographs, and Clippings
    - Women and Power Conference Scrapbook, 2001 (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Program email correspondence, 2001 (2 folders) (Box 3)
      Contact list and information about members.
    - Newspaper articles: Women's Studies and Sexism, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
    - Duke Women's Studies Program Photo Scrapbook, 1984-1992 (3 folders) (Box 3)
      Photographs of program meetings, events and miscellaneous.
    - Women's Studies Photo Scrapbook, 1983-1999 (3 folders) (Box 3)
      Photographs of staff and students (classes and retreats).
    - Loose scrapbook materials about O'Barr and Women's Studies Program, 1979-1998 (3 folders) (Box 4)
  - Publications
    - Women's Studies, 1989-1999 (6 folders) (Box 4)
      Published by or about Women's Studies at Duke.
    - About O'Barr or Women's Studies, 1974-2008 (7 folders) (Box 4)
- Accession (2011-0010), 1964-2005, 8 boxes
  Accession includes reviews of other women's studies programs throughout the United States; pamphlets and projects relating to the Women's Studies Department; materials relating to the founding of SIGNS magazine; student papers discussing gender; published and unpublished articles by O'Barr, including surveys of women at Duke, writings by O'Barr related to her African studies, and articles about women in academia and the workplace; graduate studies by O'Barr relating to Africa and anthropology; book reviews; and other miscellaneous material.
  - Reviews of Other Women's Studies Programs
    - Arizona State University, April 2001 (Box 5)
    - Appalachian State University, October 1994 (Box 5)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, January 1998 (Box 5)
    - California Polytechnic State University, January 1992 (Box 5)
    - University of California, Santa Barbara, February 2002 (Box 5)
    - Colby College, February 1995 (Box 5)
    - University of Colorado, February 1992 (Box 5)
    - Dartmouth College, April 1997 (Box 5)
    - Elon College, June 1993 (Box 5)
    - Furman University, June 1990 (Box 5)
    - Greensboro College, March 1999 (Box 5)
    - Friends of KU Women's Studies, University of Kansas, September 1994 (Box 5)
    - University of Maine, April 2004 (Box 5)
    - North Carolina State University, June 1989 (Box 5)
    - Princeton University, November 1998 (Box 5)
    - University of Texas at Dallas, April 2001 (Box 5)
    - University of Texas at San Antonio, November 1993 (Box 5)
    - University of Virginia, March 1995 (Box 5)
    - University of Virginia, February 2005 (Box 5)
    - Western Kentucky University, February 1995 (Box 5)
    - University of Wisconsin, April 1998 (Box 5)
    - Notes on program review--update, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Appalachian State University, June 2006 (Box 5)
    - East Carolina University, Fall 2006 (Box 5)
  - Special Women's Studies Projects
    - Interdisciplinary articles, Spring 2001 (Box 5)
    - Utah correspondence, May-July 1994 (Box 5)
    - Notes on mentoring, 1997-2000 (Box 5)
    - Board memberships, 1999-2000 (Box 5)
    - Feminisms conference: Sallie Bingham, 2005 (Box 5)
    - Title VI Proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 5)
    - Title VI Global Women grant, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Park School Project, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Arizona State University: The Next 25 years: A Conference on Women's Studies Program Administration, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Literature review: Graduate Scholars, September 1998 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Associates co-director, 1995-1997 (Box 5)
    - Women's Studies videotape, 1996-1997 (Box 5)
    - Women's Studies t-shirts, 1991 (Box 5)
    - Fundraising ideas, 1995-1998 (Box 5)
    - Program ideas, 1995-1997 (Box 5)
    - Feminist economics, 1996-1999 (Box 5)
    - Humanities Administrations, 1991-1997 (Box 5)
    - Alumni/ae Program coordinators, 1993-1994 (Box 5)
    - Special Events Committee, 1994-1999 (Box 5)
    - Women's Studies Instructor meetings, 1995-1998 (Box 5)
  - Photographs
    - Photos of Richard White Lecture Hall, 2001 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets
    - Issues of Comment, 1983-1986 (Box 6)
    - Tobacco Road: The Women's Issue, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Women in Higher Education, 1997-2000 (Box 6)
    - Women in Leadership and Politics, 1992-2001, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Files on SIGNS at Duke
    - Establishing SIGNS, 1985-1988 (Box 6)
    - SIGNS Selection/Appointment, 1984-1994 (Box 6)
  - Student Papers-Gender at Duke
    - Anonymous, Campus Politics of Black Faculty Initiative, undated (Box 6)
    - Jennifer Atler, house course on eating disorders, undated (Box 6)
    - Cate Baker, eating disorders (Box 6)
    - Heather Ginn, Master of Arts in Liberal Studies, single-sex schools, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Erik Ludwig, Freedom in the Duke Workplace and Classrooms, 1996 (Box 6)
    - VJ and Lisa Misol, on women and economics, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Heather Thomas, in-depth study of life as a senior, undated (Box 6)
    - Curriculum Study/Ford, Scholarship on Women and the Duke Curriculum, 1988 (Box 6)
  - Unpublished Documents Surveying Women at Duke
    - Climceer: Interim Report from the Women's Overview Planning Committee, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Women in Campus Leadership Survey, 1987 (Box 6)
    - O'Barr, "Task Force on a Duke University Women's Center," 1987 (Box 6)
    - O'Barr, "Continuing Education: Ten Years of Experience at Duke, 1969-1979" (Box 6)
    - NSF Model Project Report, 1992-1994 (Box 6)
    - Graduate Student Interviews, November 1990 (Box 6)
    - Graduate Student Survey, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Survey of Women's Studies Undergraduates, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Report on Graduate and Undergraduate Surveys, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Book Contracts
    - Permissions for Women Imagine Change, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Women Imagine Change Correspondence/Contracts, 1997-2000 (Box 6)
    - Talking Gender Correspondence/Contracts, 1994-2000 (Box 6)
    - Feminism in Action Correspondence/Contracts, 1993-2000 (Box 6)
    - Women and a New Academy, 1994-2000 (Box 6)
  - Book Reviews
    - Signs book review, 2006 (Box 6)
    - Engaging Feminism, 1992-1998 (Box 6)
    - Political Behavior in the Arab States, 1992-1994 (Box 6)
    - Language and Power, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Third World Women, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Perspective on Power, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Women and the Mau Mau in Kenya, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Africa and the Disciplines, 1993 (Box 6)
    - University of Florida Space Study, 1994 (Box 6)
    - Reconstructing the Academy, 1988-1995 (Box 6)
    - Sex and Scientific Inquiry, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Feminist Theory in Practice and Process, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Sisters and Workers in the Middle Ages, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Black Women in America, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Ties That Bind, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Educating the Majority, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Directory of Women's Studies Programs and Library Resources, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Challenging Times, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Talking Gender, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Feminism in Action, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
    - Women Imagine Change, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Published Book Reviews
    - National Council on Jewish Women: Article on Women's Studies (Box 6)
    - American Political Science Review: Sex Among Allies, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence with Alumnae, 1988-1997, 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous Letters/Professional: Praise, thank you, and sex discrimination, 1986-1993, 4 folders (Box 7)
    - Testimonials: Impact of Women's Studies (Box 7)
  - Northwestern University Graduate Studies
    - Northwestern University Graduate School Orientation Information, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Institute of World Affairs Seminar, report and photographs, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Indian Villages paper, March 1965 (Box 7)
    - Political Alienation (Master in Arts thesis), Northwestern University, 1965 (Box 7)
    - M.A/Ph.D. Exams, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
    - "The Incorporative Process," June 1965 (Box 7)
    - "Mobilization and Incorporation in Tanzania," March 1966 (Box 7)
    - Political Anthropology paper, May 1966 (Box 7)
    - Computer Keyword Indexing, Current Anthropology, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Dissertation Grant Proposals, 1965-1968 (Box 7)
    - Dissertation: "Ten House Party Cells and Their Leaders: Micropolitics in Pare District, Tanzania," 1965 (Box 8)
  - Articles (Published and Unpublished) of African Work
    - National Unity Paper, May 1969 (Box 8)
    - "Popular Patterns of Orientation to African Political Leaders and Their Impact on Local Development," African Studies Association, February 1971 (Box 8)
    - "The Role of the Ten-House Cell Leader in Rural Tanzania," African Studies Association, 1970/Geneva Afrique 1971 (Box 8)
    - "Shindano: Swahili Essays and Other Stories," Syracuse University Program of Eastern African Studies, 1971 (Box 8)
    - Conference on Rural Tanzania. Rural Africana, 1971 (Box 8)
    - "Tanu Cells and their Leaders: The Pare Case," African Studies Association meetup, 1971 (Box 8)
    - "Microlevel Political Development: Some Observations from Tanzania" American Political Science Association, 1971 (Box 8)
    - "Cell Leaders in Tanzania," Toronto, 1971/African Studies Review, 1972 (Box 8)
    - "Ujamaa: Rural Development and Socialism in Tanzania," undated (Box 8)
    - "Rural Development in Tanzania: The Political Discussion," African Studies Association, 1972 (Box 8)
    - "Pare Women: A Case of Political Involvement," Rural Africana, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
    - "Making the Invisible Visible: African Women in Politics and Policy," African Studies Review, 1975 (Box 8)
    - "Gender and Participant Citizenship: Evidence from Tunisia," Wellesley, 1976/Wisconsin-Milwaukee, 1979 (Box 8)
    - "Third World Women," Duke, 1976 (Box 8)
    - "Tanu Cells and Their Leaders," Nairobi: East African Publishing, 1976 (Box 8)
    - "Cell Leaders in Tanzania," Correspondence and Drafts, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
    - Chapters on Language and Politics, 1976-1979 (Box 8)
    - Tanzania--Uganda, The Americana Annual, 1977 (Box 8)
    - "Studying Political Participation in Rural Africa," undated (Box 8)
    - "Reflections on Forum '85 in Nairobi, Kenya," December 1985 (Box 8)
    - "African Women in Politics," African Women South of the Sahara, December 1984 (Box 8)
    - Political Economy of Development, July 1981 (Box 8)
    - "Participant Citizenship in Tunisia," Journal of Arab Affairs, 1982 (Box 8)
    - "Feminist Issues in the Fiction of Kenya's Women Writers," undated (Box 8)
    - "Men on Gender Roles: African Writing on Women in Society," undated (Box 8)
  - Articles about Education and the Workplace
    - "Second Careers for Women," Office of Continuing Education, 1975 (Box 8)
    - "Life Long Learning: The Duke Experience," Council on Aging and Human Development, 1976 (Box 8)
    - "Coping with the future," Tift, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
    - "Support for Returning Students," Adult Leadership, 1976 (Box 8)
    - "Peer Teaching Encounters Deep Disparity in Goals," Generations, Summer 1978 (Box 8)
    - "Continuing Education and the Older Learner," Center Reports on Advances in Research, Spring 1979 (Box 8)
    - "Where the Jobs Are," Redbook, May 1979 (Box 8)
    - "Conflict of Interest" Conference Book, October 1979 (Box 8)
    - "Continuing Education: Ten Years of Experience at Duke," Office of Continuing Education, 1979 (Box 8)
    - "Dual Careers at Duke," Forum for Continuing Education, Spring 1980 (Box 8)
    - Women in Higher Education, Comment, 1980 (Box 8)
    - "Funding for Adult Counseling Programs," The Forum for Continuing Education, 1980 (Box 8)
    - "Dual Learners at Duke," 1980 (Box 8)
    - "The Dual-Career Couple and Academe?," American Association for Higher Education Bulletin, 1980 (Box 8)
    - "The New Scholarship in Women: Stirring In or Stirring Up?," Duke University Letters, November 1983 (Box 8)
    - "Planning Ahead With Undergraduates: Duke Teaches a Dual Careers Course," Network News, September 1985 (Box 8)
    - "University Should Accommodate Re-Entry Women," Duke Dialogues, September 1986 (Box 8)
    - "How Did It All Begin?," Duke Institute for Learning in Retirement, 1987 (Box 8)
    - "What Does It Mean To Be An Educated Person?," AAUP Annual Convention, October 1988 (Box 8)
    - "Enriching Higher Education Locally and Nationally: Women's Centers and Women's Studies," March 1989 (Box 8)
    - Article in Japanese Newspaper. The Chunichi Shimbun, September 1989 (Box 8)
    - Office of Continuing Education: Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 8)
    - Center for Continuing Education of Women Scholars, 1983-1984 (Box 8)
    - "Women and the University," Center for Continuing Education of Women, Annual Scholarship Awards, April 1984 (Box 8)
    - Center for Continuing Education of Women Scholars, 1984-1985 (Box 8)
    - Women of Achievement Silver Medallion Award Luncheon, March 1987 (Box 8)
    - "Feminists Continue to Struggle for Place in Political Realm," The Chronicle, May 1988 (Box 8)
    - "Women's Studies and the Campus: A Contemporary Overview," June 1988 (Box 8)
    - "Success and the Southern Belle," Southern Magazine, August 1988 (Box 8)
    - Libman, Gary: "New Career Trend: She Goes, He Follows," Los Angeles Times, August 1988 (Box 8)
    - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives: Women's Education and Women's Studies Symposium, March 3-5, 1989 (Box 8)
    - "Exclusions and the Process of Empowerment: The Cases for Feminist Scholarship," May 1989 (Box 8)
    - Women's Studies issue of Duke University Libraries, Fall 1989 (Box 8)
    - "What is Women's Studies?," Trumpet of Conscience, November-December 1989 (Box 8)
    - "Women and the Politics of Knowledge," Fall 1990 (Box 8)
    - Friends Newsletter: Women's Studies at Duke University, Spring 1988-Winter 1991 (Box 8)
    - "Studying Power in Literary Texts," undated (Box 8)
    - "Men's Movement Stalks the Wild Side," Washington Post, February 1991 (Box 8)
  - Book Reviews by and about O'Barr
    - Levine, Katherine: "Tanu Cells and Social Inequality in Dar Es Salaam," 1971 (Box 8)
    - Book Reviews by Jean O'Barr (Box 8)
    - Book Reviews and Duke University Libraries, 2000-2004 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence and Planning for Miscellaneous Talks and Projects
    - Talks and Publications on Women's Studies and Education, 1992 and prior, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Pursuing Equity and Excellence, 1983(?) (Box 9)
    - Correspondence and Talks, 1976-1987 (Box 9)
    - Talks and Publications, June 1987-May 1989, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Talks and Publications, June 1989-May 1990, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Correspondence and Talks, June 1990-May 1991 (Box 9)
    - "Getting Into a Conversation About Women, Black and Ethnic Studies," 19 June 1991 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, Articles and Talks, June 1991-May 1992, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Radio Spot Soundings: "Engaging Feminism: Students Speak Up and Speak Out," March 1993 (Box 9)
    - "Leadership, Women and an Aging Society," 22 February 1993 (Box 9)
    - "Emphasizing Teaching: Whose Priority?," American Council on Education Annual Meeting, January 1993 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, Articles and Talks, June 1992-May 1993, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, Articles and Talks, June 1993-May 1994, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - "Lessons from the Majority: Women's Studies as a Model for Higher Education," October 1994 (Box 9)
    - ACE President's Conference on the New Agenda, Penn State University, June 1994 (Box 9)
    - FACA Seminar at Park School, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, Articles and Talks, June 1994-December 1994, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Comments on Receiving Teaching Award, December 1995 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, Articles and Talks, January 1995-May 1995, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, Articles and Talks, June 1995-May 1996, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, Articles and Talks, June 1995-May 1996, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, Articles and Talks, June 1996-December 1996 (Box 10)
    - Comments on Washington Women's Forum, 11 December 1996 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, Articles and Talks, January 1997-May 1997 (Box 10)
    - Talks, Consults, Presentations, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Margaret Taylor Smith Inaugural Address (not published), April 1998 (Box 10)
    - Comments on Endowment of Directorship in Honor of Margaret Taylor Smith, March 1998 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous articles on women in church and politics, June 1998-August 1998, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - "Locating Feminism" Lecture Series: Introductory Comments, 6 February 1998 (Box 10)
    - Drafts of leadership paper: "Reflections on Women as Leaders," Lamberth Conference 1998 (Box 10)
    - Articles and Events for Education, September-December 1998, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - "Naming, Sharing, Speaking," Wise Women, November 1998 (Box 10)
    - University Events and Recognitions, January-April 1999 (Box 10)
    - SIGNS Special Issue, "Feminisms at the Millennium" 1998-2000 (Box 10)
    - Articles and Events on Women and Women's Studies, May 1999 (Box 10)
    - Events and Publications on Women and the Workplace, June-August 1999 (Box 10)
    - Notes for Continuing Education Lecture, July 1999 (Box 10)
    - Women's Center Opening (not published), September, 1999 (Box 10)
    - 30th Anniversary of Continuing Education, September 28, 1999 (Box 10)
    - Women's Studies, Continuing Education and Spencer Foundation Conference, September-December 1999, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Council on Women's Studies Duke University Event in Dallas, 4 February 2000 (Box 10)